Downloaded from
YTS.BZ
Official YIFY movies site:
My name is Gudo.
I used to be a Soul Keeper.
My job was to escort
newly deceased souls to their rebirth.
But my duty changed later on.
Every departed soul
is assigned a Soul Keeper.
When they can finally
let go of the human world,
with their hands in ours...
we shepherd them
along the lake to Mount Mi.
There, they will leave
their memories behind.
After they pass through the waterfall...
They will be reincarnated.
The waterfall washes
away much of their souls.
What remains will transform into a rope.
There are usually knots on the rope.
These knots represent
their life's unresolved resentments.
I don't know what
"unresolved resentments" are,
but I do know that
they accumulate into seeds of evil.
The seeds hide inside their bodies
until they are unleashed
by rage and hatred.
Turning humans into terrifying Wraths...
Send me back, he needs me!
...but I think humans
are more complicated than that.
Seeds of evil
won't necessarily destroy them.
They may even push humans to survive.
Excuse me...
Have you seen
a little kid about this tall?
No.
My brother and I got separated,
can you help me?
Brother?
Why can't you just stay separated?
Because he's my little brother!
He's got green hair like me, and he...
One day, I met a girl named Yuri.
Not realizing she has died,
she insisted on finding her lost brother.
Okay, I'll join you on your search.
Excuse me, coming through.
Why is she showing her face here?
Shh! She'll hear us!
Father!
General Mok, why is it only you?
Where is my father?
The King is dead, long live the King!
The King died in battle?
What will happen to Flower City?
I heard that he was killed
by one of his own.
How could it be?
How can anyone kill the King?
Are we still going to fight Nyer?
How can we win without a queen and a king?
Is this caused by Goran's curse?
The Queen died when she was born.
I can't believe
this is Flower City's downfall.
Maybe she won't be the heir to the throne.
His Majesty never wanted
her to handle politics.
If she takes the throne,
will it be the end of Flower City?
Your Highness,
did the King truly mean to...
pass his throne to his cursed daughter?
You...
Your Highness,
are you all right?
What are you doing? Let me go!
What's wrong, Uncle Yin?
Goran,
we found this dagger in the King's tent!
General Mok,
did you murder the King with your dagger?
I didn't kill him!
Uncle Yin, How could it be General Mok?
It must be a misunderstanding.
Goran, everyone knows
General Mok is from Nyer.
I will kill this traitor and
avenge my brother at his funeral!
Duke, a funeral is no place
to usurp the throne!
You're in no position
to speak, kingslayer!
Take him away and execute him!
Yes, sire!
Let me go! I'm innocent!
- I can't believe it's him.
- Let me go!
The King trusted him so.
Could he have accomplices?
You can deceive a little girl,
but you can't deceive me!
You can't kill him
before an investigation!
What are you trying to do?
This is my father's funeral.
Step aside!
Goran, I am trying to
- avenge the King!
- Let me go!
Let me go and back off!
This is not what my father would want!
Your Highness!
Your Highness, what's wrong?
Kenji!
Kenji...
My name is Yuri, what's your name?
I'm Gudo.
Gudo, what is this place?
I'm worried about my little brother.
This is Another World.
- I'll help you find your brother.
- Kenji!
Gudo, are you here
because you're lost like me?
No, I live here.
Then we'll definitely find my brother!
Among all the souls I've met...
she's the first one who smiles
instead of crying in fear.
Kenji!
She often uses words
I've never heard of...
Words like...
"longing," "parting" and "hungry."
I don't know any of those words.
- I think...
- Kenji!
- ...we have to find Kenji...
...before she'll follow me
to reincarnation.
Another World is too big.
It's impossible to find Kenji.
I need a break.
Gudo, don't you get tired?
What is "tired"?
Can you hear that?
What do you mean?
My tummy's hungry.
I miss my family!
She talks about her family all the time.
Mommy's food is so yummy!
When she's tired...
- Kenji, where are you?
- ...she'd say her tummy's hungry.
I want to go home and eat!
She wants to find Kenji,
so her family can eat together again.
She'd draw a loop on her tummy.
She said it means "her tummy's hungry."
I don't remember having a family.
How do I get a "family"?
Why does Yuri see
Another World so differently?
How does it feel to be different?
What is the human realm like?
Princess, are you alright?
Your Highness, are you OK?
Am I still alive?
Of course, Princess, don't be silly.
How about my father?
Leave! All of you!
I heard General Mok wanted
to usurp the throne.
Princess, listen to me!
General Mok is innocent.
An enemy assassin did it!
Goran!
Listen, there's not much time!
What do you mean?
Thousands of Nyer troops are
stationed 10 kilometers outside our city.
According to our spy,
General Mok planned to kill the King
and colluded with Nyer.
He wants Flower City to fall.
Princess, let me execute him!
I didn't kill the King!
My father taught me
about giving benefit of the doubt.
I think we should investigate...
This is no time to hesitate!
I'll attend the briefing on your behalf.
We have to fight back.
Do you understand?
Flower City needs a capable leader.
I hope you understand.
Princess Goran.
What did you do to my father?
Why did you kill him?
I did no such thing.
Then who did it?
Why isn't anyone telling me the truth?
I don't care whether
you're colluding with Nyer.
I just want to know
what happened to my father.
If he's gone to Another World,
how do I find him?
Princess,
Flower City needs you to be strong now.
His Majesty...
he took his own life!
What?!
He couldn't bear
his injuries any longer...
Impossible! That can't be...
The journey back to the city was too long.
Shut up! You're lying!
Why would he abandon Flower City?
He didn't want to return?
Princess, that's not what I meant!
Shut up!
He would die to defend his nation!
He'd never kill himself...
- He was defending his nation...
- Shut up!
...and you as well.
That's why he... I hope you understand.
Liar!
What happened to you, Father?
Now that you're both gone,
I'm all alone...
What am I to do?
Did I kill Mother and you?!
I'm not wanted here in Flower City.
I'm a burden to you both, right?
I shouldn't have been born.
Father would never abandon Flower City.
General Mok and Uncle Yin...
they could both be lying...
Father, what would you do?
Didn't I order you to leave?
What?
Hi, Goran.
What are you? Human or ghost?
I am Gudo, I'm from Another World.
Another World...?
Are you a Soul Keeper?
Are you taking me away?
I was once a Soul Keeper
who took deceased souls to their rebirth.
But I have another duty now.
Then... have I died?
You wouldn't be here
in the human world if you had died.
Then why are you here?
Are you taking my father away?
He's dead. He's in Another World.
Then take me to Another World!
I need my father!
Only he can save Flower City now.
I will trade my life for his!
Flower City needs him, not me.
Why?
You didn't kill anyone.
What do you know?
Your mother died during childbirth,
but you didn't kill your mother.
Why are you here?
My tummy's hungry.
What?
Leave after you're done!
I'm full.
Then beat it!
I'm full!
I can grant you a favor in return.
Should I trust Uncle Yin?
I don't know.
Did General Mok lie, then?
Why would he do that?
The human world is unfathomable,
you can only keep marching on.
What are you on about?
I don't understand.
I can take you back
to a moment in the past.
A moment in the past?
You can see something
that has already happened.
Then take me
to the moment before Father died.
I need to see who murdered him.
All right.
Father!
Goran!
- It's him! It's really him!
- Goran, don't go!
Gudo, let her through.
I'll kill this Wrath in one blow!
Dark Sky, wait!
If you ask me,
I've no idea why you're dawdling.
Out of my way.
Dark Sky, stop!
You're not in charge here!
Step aside!
Father!
He killed my father!
- No!
- I'll make him pay!
Let me go!
Goran!
Goran, pull yourself together!
Pull yourself together!
That's not the whole truth.
You have to keep watching.
Wake up, Goran!
Gudo, stop protecting that Wrath!
She has no evil horn!
She's not a Wrath yet!
I'm so close...
Close to what?
Pulling her seed of evil?
Gudo, she's seen the truth.
You can't change anything!
If I find her knots,
I can pull the seed of evil!
I'm close!
You can't stop human hatred!
Once the seed of evil grows,
it's too late!
Get out of my way!
Three!
Two!
One!
If you ask me, those with
seeds of evil are Wraths already.
They are nothing but disasters!
They're not born this way!
A seed of evil grows for a reason!
The Goddess said
that before the seed grows horns...
I can still help her!
And you cannot hurt her!
It's him...
He killed my father...
He deserves to die... I want revenge!
Goran!
Goran, wake up!
You haven't seen the whole truth yet!
Out of my way!
This is because you're a Wrath!
That's a wrap.
Gudo!
Huh?
Why are we here?
I'm taking you to the Goddess.
The Goddess?
She knows everything about Another World.
She will know where to find your brother.
What are these?
When deceased souls reincarnate,
they leave behind these ropes.
These are the only things they leave
behind in Another World.
Why are there knots on the ropes?
Everyone carries regrets...
and unresolved rage.
Accumulating too much
will form seeds of evil.
Seeds of evil?
What happens to those with seeds of evil?
Balance rules all things.
When a seed of evil hides
in a human's heart...
they either become a Wrath...
or a light ray.
We untie the knot
to minimize the damage
caused by Wraths.
Let me explain, Goddess!
Gudo said that she isn't a Wrath yet,
but her seed's sprouted.
He used his powers on me!
No offense, but he has ulterior motives!
I only attacked her for our own good.
If you ask me, I never trust humans.
I don't care if she has horns.
I've been killing Wraths for years,
and I'm sure that Goran
will become a Wrath!
Dark Sky,
do you remember
your promise to protect Gudo?
I do, but if you ask me...
Dark Sky, stop speaking for a minute.
Gudo.
You can still...
I have to save her.
I promised her.
The hatred and anger
contained in a seed...
can change one's nature.
Are you sure you can do this?
I believe in her.
I will stay in the human world.
I can pull her seed of evil.
Her horns haven't grown,
she won't become a Wrath.
If you have faith in humanity,
you must witness what happens next.
To pull this off,
you must understand
human nature and timing.
Flower City needs a capable leader now...
...and it won't be you!
General Mok might have killed the King.
But you are the real murderer!
Don't do it, Your Highness!
Once upon a time,
Flower City had a cursed princess.
When she learned
that her father was killed,
Her anger compelled the Wrath
to share his destructive power with her.
For the sake of vengeance,
darkness overtook Flower City overnight.
All the flowers in the city withered.
She became known as the "Ghost Princess."
Soon after she went missing,
Flower City was conquered.
No one ever saw
the "Ghost Princess" again.
Without the "Ghost Princess,"
Flower City became Wheat Village.
Wrath, my lord...
please share your power with me.
It's time! We can't wait anymore!
This year's harvest has been disastrous.
Remember, it is your privilege
to contribute to Nyer.
You must submit half your harvest
by noon tomorrow.
Anyone who lies about your harvest,
which has happened before,
your head will roll!
Slacking off?
Get up and work! Now!
Get up now!
Get up now, you hear me?
Don't play dead, you bastard!
Get up! Right now!
General!
We won't survive winter
if you take half the harvest!
Please have mercy!
Keung, where are you going?
Headed up the mountain?
Why are you going up?
It's covered in snow!
I'm off to find food!
You're off to Requiem Temple, aren't you?!
Don't go! They'll kill your family!
They're already killing us!
Don't go, Keung!
There's a scary "ghost hand" there!
So what if you find a Wrath?
You'll get us all killed.
We can't just wait for death!
They want half when we barely have enough.
It'll only get worse!
Life's only become harder
the last 30 years.
You won't survive the winter.
I'll go to Requiem Temple and
ask the Wrath to make me fearsome.
Then I can force them...
to open the barn and return our food!
Duan...
Keung is doing this
for all of Wheat Village.
You may not have the courage to fight,
but don't hold him back.
If he gets caught, we're all dead.
You may not care about your life,
but think of the others!
My little girl.
Mama!
Where is Papa going?
Let's go home.
Let your father go.
You can't eat this!
It'll hurt your tummy.
A Wrath's no joke!
Hey!
Come back!
Gudo.
I can smell a Wrath here.
Goddess, can you help Yuri
find her brother?
Gudo, your job is to guide deceased
souls to their reincarnation.
Why are you helping her find her brother?
Please help me!
How did he get lost?
He went missing four days ago.
Gudo, I'm granting you
the power to see the past.
You'll be able to help Yuri
find her brother.
However, you can only see the past,
you cannot change it.
Wrath, my lord! Please help us!
We've no other way!
Please turn me into a Wrath!
Why would you want to be a Wrath?
Wrath, my lord!
I am Gudo, not a Wrath!
Lord Gudo!
I want to be a vicious Wrath!
Then I can scare those bastards
and save everyone!
Why do you have to save everyone?
The truth is, my lord,
we're at our wits' end.
If I don't step up, who will?
Why must it be a Wrath?
I must be as fearsome
as the Ghost Princess
to scare those bastards.
"Ghost Princess"?
Do you mean Princess Goran?
Yes, I heard that she's a Wrath
who killed all who betrayed her.
She was not a Wrath, she was just a girl.
An unfortunate girl.
Ghost Princess!
You're a Wrath!
Why is the Princess doing this to us?
What am I doing?
Goran, if you want,
we can go back again.
I want to see my father.
Leave...
before they get here.
Your Majesty!
Let me stay behind.
Nyer's army will arrive soon.
If you return to Flower City,
you can get help.
There's only one way...
Use my corpse to stall for time...
I'll get you home!
Your Majesty, stay strong!
Goran is waiting for you in Flower City.
The whole nation needs you!
Take Goran far away!
Your Majesty!
Doctor!
Father!
Father, why?
Don't die, Father!
Goran.
You've seen the truth...
Why isn't it working?
Go...ran...
Your mother was ill even before
she gave birth to you.
Your birth was our miracle.
The cursed one is this place, not you.
Forgive me for never
getting over your mother,
and failing to take good care of you.
Stay alive,
so you can protect your people.
I know you've tried hard
all these years...
I know that.
Burn the corpses! Now!
Yes, sir!
Should I take this arrowhead home?
Yeah.
- Don't come closer!
- Go away!
Go hide! Right now!
There must be another way...
I need to find Uncle Yin,
then we'll stop Nyer and save Flower City.
We can do it.
We can do it...
I need... I need to...
Gudo, what are you doing?
Your only mission is to pull
her seed of evil.
But why didn't her life change
for the better?
Whether or not she has a seed of evil,
her life is in her own hands...
You have nothing to do with it.
For some odd reason,
I sense my heart shattering.
Gudo, my lord? My lord?
Oh.
Are you still deciding
whether to turn me into a scary Wrath?
Being a Wrath is not what you think.
Goran was not a Wrath,
and neither are you.
Wraths bring nothing but tragedies!
Do you know the story
behind the "Ghost Hand"?
It must've belonged to a fierce Wrath.
He was a desperate Wrath.
Do you know whose blood this is?
I'll take you 300 years into the past,
so you can see it yourself.
Then you can decide
whether you still want to become a Wrath.
Anything you say, my lord.
But...
But what?
My tummy's hungry.
Seriously?
I don't have any food on me...
Wait, that reminds me...
Weird enough, I found this on my way here.
I'll give you half.
Keung, please remember who...
and what you are.
For the village's safety,
you cannot take away the sacrifices.
My daughter is not a sacrifice!
How can you kill one of your own?
Catch him!
Think of the entire village,
not just yourself!
Don't kill us, please...
Papa! Papa has become a monster!
Our prayers are answered!
The Wrath is here!
He will save us from the battle!
No, Lord Wrath, don't attack us!
Help!
Guards!
Ha! Serves you right!
Cut the other arm, too!
Let me go!
I can't run anymore...
Papa? Papa!
No!
Stop! That's your daughter!
What is happening?
Being a Wrath is not what you think.
This won't happen to me,
I can control myself.
Wraths cannot stop killing...
until their evil horns are chopped off.
I'll recognize my own daughter!
This won't happen to me!
I can save my family!
That Wrath had weak willpower!
It won't happen to me!
No one but me can save my family.
Lord Gudo...
please turn me into a Wrath...
I won't forget my family!
Gudo!
Stop!
I told you there's a Wrath here...
Duan?!
Too slow!
I'll chop off your evil horns!
Time to die!
So you've got some moves after all.
Keung!
There must be another way!
Don't get carried away!
Gudo, stop sleeping and come help!
If we don't kill this Wrath now,
Another World will suffer.
If his victims' souls all drift
to Another World,
it may create more Wraths!
I have an idea.
But we only have one shot at it.
I can scream, too!
Don't say I never help you!
Ann!
Ann, take my hand!
Kara!
Hold on tight!
Help us, Dad!
Duan...
- Kara!
- Duan!
Dad!
Gudo, my lord...
are you telling me that...
turning into a Wrath won't save us?
What should I do?
If Wheat Village bands together,
we may stand a chance...
Keung!
Where are you? Come back!
Let's get them together!
We'll reclaim what we deserve!
Lord Gudo...
I'm done with becoming a Wrath,
I want to stay human!
I want to reclaim our food
with the others!
Lord Gudo, where are you?
Lord Gudo!
Promise me you won't turn me into a Wrath!
You're weak, Gudo.
I told you
there's more than one Wrath out here!
The number of Wraths will never exceed
human's evil thoughts.
They reap what they sow.
I wonder what will happen to Keung.
Gudo, he's a mere mortal
who will reach an inevitable end.
I don't know why you're being...
whatever this is...
We made a pact...
A pact for what?
Passed out again?
You're lucky you've got me!
Open the barn!
Corrupted scum!
My lord, all the peasants have come.
Stay back!
If you take one step forward,
I'll kill him!
Fire the arrows.
Please stop!
You'll kill one of your own!
Save me first!
I cut off my own arm to show you
that it is not a Wrath's arm!
It doesn't belong in Requiem Temple!
I want to show everybody...
I lost more than an arm today.
We also lost countless loved ones...
and those who died of hunger!
We stand before you...
as the last farmers of Wheat Village.
We're united for a common cause...
to reclaim what is rightfully ours!
And we are ready to do whatever it takes!
If nobody farms,
there will be no food for anyone.
We will all dine in hell!
So, I ask you one last time...
will you open the barn door?!
You low-lives!
Hmph! Open the barn!
Watch out!
Let me out! Help!
Help! Let me out!
What's that noise?
Let me check.
It's a Wrath! Help!
Yuri, wait for me!
Where are you?
Kenji!
Yuri!
Yuri! Where did you go?
Wait for me!
Kenji!
Gudo!
Yuri!
Oh, wow!
This place is so interesting!
Come on.
What are you looking at? Get up!
I'd like to show you something.
So... am I long dead?
Your body is just an illusion.
It's all just an illusion?
So my death is also an illusion?
Death is just a temporary state.
You will reincarnate and live again.
What about those in my memories?
Only your feelings are real.
They hide deep in your soul.
Like how I want to find my little brother?
How about you?
Huh?
Are you an illusion too?
I am a...
Goddess?! Goddess?!
What happened? I'll save you!
I thought we'd pulled the seed of evil!
All these millennia, I still haven't
eradicated human hatred...
brutality, cruelty,
resentment, hostility...
The Wraths' evil have consumed humanity,
so Another World must endure this.
All things are unfathomable,
but they can only keep marching on.
Goddess, there's no time to talk zen!
Get to the point! How do we get you out?
Untie Gudo's knot first,
a miracle awaits.
Gudo, where is your knot?
Give it to me!
My knot?
What now? Is your knot metaphorical?
What should we do now?
I don't know how to untie knots,
I only know how to kill Wraths.
What is happening to Another World?
These are the red ropes
left by deceased souls.
When Keung's villagers fought,
someone became a Wrath.
Everyone died!
How about Keung?
Did they succeed?
If they did,
Another World wouldn't be in trouble!
And the Goddess?
She's tangled up in the ropes,
I can't sever them.
She said I must untie your knot.
Gudo, think!
I know it is weird for you
since you are not a human.
But is it possible that you
have untied knots?
Are you ready?
Gudo...
I will go with you.
Okay!
Please don't take it!
Give it back!
Beat it!
Kenji...
Kenji, open your mouth...
You have to drink.
Kenji...
Go away!
We don't have any food.
Kenji.
Where's Kenji?
His life extended your life.
Humans must eat
when their tummies are hungry.
You don't have to be sad.
But he's my brother!
Yuri!
What is this?
It's so hot!
You're Yuri, you do this
when your tummy's hungry!
You're Yuri,
your mother is a great cook!
Yuri!
You're Yuri, you still have to find
your brother and reincarnate!
Wake up!
Gudo, what is happening to me?
I don't know.
But you are fine now...
Yuri, your seed of evil
has sprouted in Another World after all.
After seeing the truth,
I thought she would reincarnate.
Instead, it triggered her transformation
into a Wrath.
Goddess, Yuri is not a Wrath.
She's seen her brother.
I can take her to reincarnation.
Gudo, you don't understand.
Her seed of evil has sprouted.
Souls with seeds of evil
cannot reincarnate.
No! I must help her reincarnate!
Gudo... what should we do?
I'll take you to your next life!
You'll see your brother again!
She cannot stay in Another World,
and she cannot reincarnate...
she has to stay here...
and crumble into dust...
Yuri!
Goddess!
Please help her!
Gudo!
What should we do now?
Waah...! Waah...!
What are you doing, Gudo?
I'm trying to cry like you.
I'm scared I'll never see my family
and Kenji again...
When I think of never seeing you again...
I begin to understand.
Waah...! Waah...!
Ken...ji...
Are they still here?
No.
What happened here?
Mother Earth...
why do people have seeds of evil?
It all started with wisdom...
when human beings began
to differentiate good from evil.
So human beings are the source
of the seed of evil?
They wanted to use destructive powers...
to right all that they saw as wrong.
Then how do we remove their seeds of evil?
All things come apart when causes
and conditions dissipate.
Yuri wants to reincarnate,
but she has a seed of evil in her.
Souls reincarnating with seeds of evil...
must live through a millennium.
No matter how many times they reincarnate,
they still carry it?
Gudo,
you heard what Mother Earth said.
If Yuri's second evil horn grows,
her power will threaten not only
the human world...
but also Another World.
But if I pull the seeds of evil
from each of her lives,
she can reincarnate into a normal person
after a millennium.
People change.
Yuri already has one evil horn.
You're sure her seed won't sprout
over the next millennium?
I will stay with her!
Every time she reincarnates,
her seed grows more powerful.
It's only 1,000 years.
It will not be easy.
I can do it.
If Yuri turns into a Wrath,
both you and Yuri
will crumble into dust...
I won't give up!
Are you sure you want to do this, Gudo?
I have faith in her.
Yuri, if you want
to save your little brother,
you must forget him.
If I let him go,
he'll be saved?
Yuri,
to see him again,
you have to reincarnate.
To reincarnate,
you have to forget him.
So, rebirth is
the only way to see him again?
I want to be reborn! I want a rebirth!
Gudo,
remember your promise of a thousand years.
I will!
What are these?
Your memories.
I don't think I've seen these...
Memories are too heavy.
You have to leave them here.
Otherwise...
you cannot cross over.
Once you cross...
you'll see your brother again.
Okay!
Wait for me.
Will I forget you?
Yuri,
after you pass the waterfall,
you will enter your next life.
How about you?
I promise...
no matter where you go,
I'll find you.
Will I remember you?
How will I recognize you?
Gudo!
In the next millennium,
no matter where you go...
I'll find you.
I promise...
I will find you.
So, both Goran and Keung
are Yuri's reincarnations.
And there were others before them.
I remember them.
So, a millennium has passed...
Soul Keepers cannot enter
the human world so many times.
That's why you are so weak...
We have a pact.
But she doesn't recognize you...
I recognize her, we have a pact!
If you ask me,
I'd say you're wasting your time.
No offense, but I have an ulterior motive.
Ha! You copycat!
I will find her.
This is her last life in the millennium.
I get it now! She's your "knot"!
But what if you die this time?
Is it worth it?
You'll crumble into dust.
I promised Goddess to protect you.
My head hurts, and I'm headless!
If humans can reincarnate,
and if I crumble into dust,
will my knot return to Mount Mi?
If you ask me,
I'd say crumbling into dust
means nothing's left.
If Yuri turns into a Wrath,
what should I do?
You'll stop her!
But fair warning,
if she turns into a Wrath,
I have to kill her.
I have faith that she won't
turn into a Wrath.
Then let's go.
You have a pact!
And I have to save Goddess.
Eat something, or you'll starve!
But I only like your cooking.
You're just using my food
to feed your cat.
Let's go! Back to work!
Look, the stuff from the chimneys
look like my hair.
I told you to get some rest
in Another World.
You don't need to be here all the time
and exhaust yourself.
I'll be fine, I want to see Ying at work.
What's there to see?
They just stand there and weave.
But...
Fine, I'll take you there later.
I can smell a Wrath over there,
Dark Sky...
You're so useless!
What are you doing?
None of your work passes muster!
You're breaking the machine!
Scram if you're not up to it!
Don't drag us down!
Mark, what's with you?
The supervisor's absence
doesn't mean you're in charge!
It's always you two!
You're why they cut our meal tickets!
You hear that?
Don't listen to him.
We'll fix them, mind your own business!
Nana...
Exactly, your incompetence
shouldn't be our business!
But we all starve because of it!
That's right!
Stop dragging us down!
Where can they go?
They are just like us...
sold to be child workers here.
Hardy, you wanna be a hero?
Are you done?
- You bullies!
- Nana, stop...
You stinking orphans!
You hit me!
Stop!
Nana, just ignore them...
Are you done? Leave us alone!
It's all because of you!
Stop! Stop!
Don't hurt my sister!
Stop, Mark!
Back off!
Nana!
Ying, stay where you are!
Stay back!
There's a Wrath? I would know.
It's just Ying's factory.
Go take a look.
Ying!
Nana!
That's so hot!
This way! Be careful!
Nana?
Why did my sister die?
Is it because of me?
It's because of me!
I killed my sister!
Fire! Help!
Ying!
That escalated quickly!
Where are you, Ying?
Ying!
Ying, what are you doing? Let's go!
It's dangerous here.
Ying!
Do you remember this?
Don't turn into a Wrath!
Your name is Yuri! Do you remember?
I'm Gudo! Do you remember?
We're so close! Wake up!
Wake up, Yuri!
I promised
we'd find your brother together!
Kenji...
Do you remember me, Yuri?
I'm sorry, Gudo!
She's no longer Yuri!
Yuri, no!
Yuri!
Hey, can you hear that?
Look...
that's...
Yuri, you have to stop!
Dark Sky, no...
We still have a chance...
Stop, Yuri!
Don't force my hand!
Na...na...
I really will kill you!
Snap out of it!
I guess that's it!
No, Dark Sky! She's still human!
Get out of my way!
Gudo, why'd you stop me?!
If we don't kill the Wrath now,
both the human world and Another World
will be destroyed!
We missed our chance!
Because you were naïve enough
to think you can save her!
You broke my sword!
Should I fight her with my bare hands?
Open your eyes and take a look!
Does she look like a human to you?
She may look like Yuri or Ying,
but she's a Wrath now.
If her evil horns are sealed,
it's all over!
Not just this place!
Another World and Goddess, too!
Forget this!
Yuri... Don't turn into a Wrath...
Do you remember?
I know what you are trying to do!
Stop!
Why are you so heavy, you bag of bones?
Let's chop those evil horns off!
Dark Sky...
Gudo! If you make it back
to Another World and see Goddess...
you have to tell her...
I did my best to protect you!
Sorry, Gudo.
I have to kill her now!
This thing's a tough one.
Yuri...
Don't do this!
I'm Gudo...
Do you remember me?
It's worth it.
These thousand years... was all worth it!
Who am I?
Yuri.
Yuri?
Who am I?
After you pass the waterfall,
you will enter your next life.
How about you?
I promise, wherever you go,
I will find you.
Will I remember you?
Your name is Yuri, you died on a mountain.
You were looking
for your little brother then.
My little brother...
I ate...
I...
I ate my little brother?
You have to forgive yourself!
That's the only way I can take away
your seed of evil.
Yuri, don't blame yourself!
They're acts of fate!
I remember now! I killed so many people!
So many died because of me!
I killed so many people!
I'm an evil person!
You didn't send them to their deaths!
You just couldn't save them!
I'm not worthy of forgiveness...
Yuri!
Look at your hands, who are you grabbing?
Look at who you're grabbing!
Yuri!
Kenji?
Ying saved you...
I saved you in this life?
Am I qualified to offer salvation?
Anyone can offer salvation,
you just need to have faith
in time and yourself.
You have kindness in you,
you just forgot about it.
The aura of the Wrath is gone...
Ying! Ying...
Ying! Are you all right?
I recognize you...
You remember me? That's right, it's Hardy!
I've been looking for you
for a thousand years!
Gudo, hey...
Gu... Gudo...
Gudo, hang in there!
There's no time!
It's too late!
Gudo,
all the knots in Another World
have been untied.
Goddess.
Does that mean
I'll soon crumble into dust?
Gudo...
we made a pact.
I didn't forget about you.
You know how to cry now!
Goddess, can Yuri be
a normal person again?
Can she reincarnate now?
Yes.
I can't be in the human world...
nor Another World now.
It's all over.
There's another way.
You can reincarnate and
become a human being.
Do I have to forget...
the past millennium?
So this is how the sorrow
of parting feels...
I get it now.
ANOTHER WORLD
If you ask me,
I'd say you're wasting your time.
It's okay, I'll watch over him from here.